（至今走过的路）
我一生都在寻找这个恶魔
Look, our whole lives we've been searching for this demon.
现在终于有了线索
We finally know where this demon's gonna be…
也知道如何结果它
and now we know how to kill him.
我要结束这一切
This ends now. I'm ending it.
一定要结束
I don't care what it takes.
无论用什么方法
No matter what method.
幻象
A vision.
不管我看到没看到 事实是
Visions or no visions, the fact is…
这个恶魔今晚就会出现
the demon is coming tonight.
而那家人会像我们一样经历一切
And this family's gonna go through the same hell we went through.
我们知道你有那把枪 约翰
We know you have the gun, John.
你刚刚是在向我们宣战
You just declared war.
我会给你们柯尔特
l'll bring you the Colt.
那个恶魔今晚就会来
The demon is coming.
我们只有那把枪
That gun is all we got.
你想给梅格一把假枪 指望她不会发现？
Hand Meg a fake gun, hope she doesn't notice.
我们等待这一仗很长时间了
I've been waiting a long time for this fight.
听着 今晚没人会死 我们不会 那家人也不会
Nobody's dying tonight. Not us, not that family.
为什么不把枪交出来
Why don't you hand over the gun.
也许我该射你
Maybe l'll just shoot you.
来的可不止我一个
There's more where I came from.
它来了
It's coming.
我不敢相信你竟然射了我
I can't believe you just shot me!
这是赝品
It's a fake.
萨姆 不
Sam, no.
迪恩 让我去 它还在里面
Let me go. It's still in there.
你进去就是自杀
You get in there It's suicide.
我不在乎
l don't care.
我在乎
l do.
那东西杀死了杰西
That thing killed Jess.
杀死了妈妈
That thing killed Mom.
她们都已经不在了 再也不会回来了
They're gone. And they're never coming back.
经历了那么多事 不许你再这么说
Don't you say that.Not after all this.
你们俩这次可真把事给搞砸了
You boys really screwed up this time.
他在哪
Where is he.
你们永远也见不到你们父亲了
You're never gonna see your father again.
它们抓住了爸爸
They've got Dad.
梅格
Meg.
她说什么了
What'd she say.
我刚跟你说了 萨姆
l just told you, Sammy.
好吧
Okay.
你在干嘛 迪恩
What are you doing, Dean.
我们必须离开
We gotta go.
为什么
Why.
因为那个恶魔知道我们在拯救郡
The demon knows we're in Salvation.
他还知道柯尔特在我们身上
It knows we've got the Colt.
现在它抓了爸爸 很可能下一个就来找咱们了
It's got Dad. It's coming for us.
那才好 我们还有三发子弹 让它来吧
Good. We've got three bullets left.
听着 勇士 我们还没有准备好
Listen, we're not ready.
我们也不知道它们有多少人
We don't know how many of them are out there.
要是我们死了 就什么也做不成了
Now, we're no good to anybody dead.
我们走… 立刻
We're leaving. Now.
我告诉你 迪恩 我们可以结果那家伙的
l'm telling you, we could've taken them.
我们需要的是一个计划
What we need is a plan.
关键是它们还没杀死爸爸 我们要找到关他的地方
They're probably keeping Dad alive. Just gotta figure out where.
它们想用爸爸来换枪
They'll wanna trade him for the gun.
怎么了
What.
如果真是那样的话 为什么梅格一点不提交易的事呢
Dean, if that were true. why didn't Meg mention a trade.
- 爸爸他可能 - 不要说了
- Dad, he might be - Don't.
我也不愿意这是真的
Look, I don't wanna believe it any more than you…
但如果真是这样 我们就更该杀了这个恶魔
but if he is, all the more reason to kill this damn thing.
柯尔特还在我们手上 我们还有机会
We still have the Colt. We can finish the job.
现在不是谈这件事的时候 萨姆
Screw the job, Sam.
迪恩 我只是觉得该做爸爸想让我们做的事
I'm just trying to do what he'd want.
他一定会希望我们继续的
He would want us to keep going.
你能不能别再说得好像他已经死了
Quit talking about him like he's dead.
听着
Listen to me.
在我们救他回来之前 其他一切免谈
everything stops until we get him back.
你明白吗 一切事情
Do you understand me Everything.
好吧 那你准备怎么找他
So how do we find him.
我们去林肯
We go to Lincoln.
从他被抓走的那个仓库开始找
Start at the warehouse where he was taken.
你真觉得恶魔会在那里留下线索
Come on. You really think these demons are gonna leave a trail.
没错 它不会
You're right.
我们得找人帮忙
We need help.
给你
Here you go.
什么东西 圣水
What is this, holy water.
那瓶是 这瓶是威士忌
That one is. This is whiskey.
谢谢 鲍比 感谢你所做的一切
Bobby, thanks. Thanks for everything.
说真的 我不知道我们该不该来这
l wasn't sure if we should come.
别说傻话 你们父亲需要帮助
Nonsense. Your daddy needs help.
上次我们来这
Yeah, but last time we saw you, I mean,
你的确威胁说要用铅弹打爆他的头
you did threaten to blast him.
还把散弹枪什么的都用上了
You cocked the shotgun and everything.
是啊 没错 我不否认
Yeah, well, what can I say.
约翰就是有那种能耐
John just has that effect on people.
是啊 他的确有
Yeah, I guess he does.
现在过去的都不重要了
None of that matters now.
唯一要紧的是 你们能把他救出来
All that matters is that you get him back.
鲍比 这本书
Bobby, this book…
我从没读到过类似的东西
l've never seen anything like it.
所罗门之钥
Key of Solomon.
说实话 这些才是真东西
It's the real deal, all right.
这些保护圈 真的有用吗？
And these These protective circles, they really work.
当然
Hell, yeah.
如果一个魔怪进入其中 它就被困住了
You get a demon in one, they're trapped. Powerless.
变得毫无法力 这就像个恶魔监狱
It's like a satanic roach motel.
放心吧 这个人知道自己在干什么
Man knows his stuff.
我还要告诉你们一件事
I'll tell you something else too.
你们将要对付的东西非常棘手
This is some serious crap you boys stepped in.
哦 为什么
Oh, yeah.
那会是怎样的
How's that.
以往一年
Normal year, I hear of…
大约只有三起魔鬼附身的事件发生
say, three demonic possessions.
- 最多四起 - 是
- Maybe four, tops. - Yeah.
但今年 目前为止 我已经听到27起了
This year, I heard of 27 so far.
明白我的意思吗
You get what l'm saying.
越来越多的魔鬼出现在人间 远远超过以前
More and more demons are walking among us.A lot more.
你知道为什么吗
Do you know why.
不知道 但我确定会有大事发生
No, but I know it's something big.
山雨欲来
Storm's coming.
而你们和你们父亲
And you boys and your daddy…
正处于漩涡中心
you are smack in the middle of it.
拉姆斯·菲尔德
Rumsfeld.
怎么回事
What is it.
有些不对劲
Something's wrong.
我们别再废话了 行吗
No more crap, okay.
我要柯尔特 萨姆 真正的柯尔特
I want the Colt, Sam.The real Colt.
现在就要
Right now.
不在我们身上 我们把它埋了
We don't have it on us. We buried it.
我记得已经说过「别再废话」了
Didn't I say, "No more crap"
我发誓 在和你们一家人打交道这么久之后
I swear, after everything I heard about you Winchesters…
我必须说 我对你们已经没有任何兴趣了
l gotta tell you, I'm a little underwhelmed.
先是约翰想用把假枪忽悠我们
First Johnny tries to pawn off a fake gun…
然后他还把真枪留给了你们这两个笨蛋
and then he leaves the real gun with you two chuckleheads.
极不明智
Lackluster, man.
我说 你们真以为我找不到这里
I mean, did you really think I wouldn't find you.
事实上 我们正等着呢
Actually, we were counting on it.
抓住你了
Gotcha.
《邪恶力量》
知道么 如果你们想要我留下来
You know, if you wanted to tie me up.
只要说一句就行了
all you had to do was ask.
我在窗户和门前都撒了盐
I salted the doors and windows.
即使她还有帮手 它们也进不来
If there are any demons out there, they aingt getting in.
我们的爸爸在哪里 Meg
Where's our father, Meg.
你问得不够有礼貌
You didn't ask very nice.
我们的爸爸在哪里 婊子
Where's our father, bitch.
天啊 你就用那张嘴亲你母亲的？
Jeez, you kiss your mother with that mouth.
哦 我忘了 你没那机会
Oh, I forgot. You don't.
你觉得这只是个吓唬你的游戏
Hey, you think this is a frigging game.
他在哪 你们把他怎么样了
Where is he What did you do to him.
他尖叫着死去
He died screaming.
我亲手杀的他
I killed him myself.
那真叫人吃惊 你竟然打女孩子
That's kind of a turn on, you hitting a girl.
你不是女孩子
You're no girl.
迪恩
Dean.
你没事吧
You okay.
她说谎 他没死
She's lying. He's not dead.
迪恩 你要小心点对付她 别伤着她
Dean, you gotta be careful with her. Don't hurt her.
为什么
Why.
因为她的确是个女孩子 那就是为什么
Because she really is a girl, that's why.
你在说什么
What are you talking about.
她只是被附身了
She's possessed.
那是个被魔鬼附身的人
That's a human possessed by a demon.
你们看不出吗
Can't you tell.
你不是想告诉我有个无辜的女孩子
You trying to tell me there's an innocent girl.
被困在那个身体里吧
trapped somewhere in there.
真是个好消息
That's actually good news.
你要给我读故事吗
You gonna read me a story.
差不多 开始吧 萨姆
Something like that. Hit it, Sam.
驱逐咒 你没开玩笑吧
An exorcism Are you serious.
你说的没错 宝贝 头晕
We're going for it, baby. Head spinning.
目眩 呕吐 痛苦可多着呢
projectile vomiting, the whole nine yards.
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you.
我要把你剥皮拆骨
I'm gonna rip the bones from your body.
不 你会死在地狱的烈火中
No, you're gonna burn in hell.
除非你告诉我们 我们爸爸在哪里
Unless you tell us where our dad is.
好吧 至少你能得到身不错的黑皮肤
Well, at least you'll get a nice tan.
他满含着眼泪 乞求不要杀他
He begged for his life with tears in his eyes.
乞求见你们两个最后一面
He begged to see his sons one last time.
就在那时我割断了他的喉咙
That's when I slit his throat.
为你自己着想 我希望你说的不是真的
For your sake, I hope you're lying.
否则的话 我向上帝发誓
Because if it's true, I swear to God…
我一定亲自去地狱
l will march into hell myself and I will slaughter.
撕碎你们这群狗娘养的混蛋
each and every one of you evil sons of bitches, so help me, God.
他在哪
Where is he.
你就是不接受「他死了」这个事实 是不是
You just won't take dead for an answer. Where is he.
他在哪
Where is he.
死了 不 他没有
Dead No, he's not!
他没死 他不会死的
He's not dead. He can't be!
你在看什么？继续读啊
What are you looking at Keep reading.
他就快死了
He will be!
等等 你说什么
Wait! What.
他还没死
He's not dead.
但在我们对他做的事情完成后 他就会死
But he will be after what we do to him.
我们怎么知道你说的是实话
How do we know you're telling the truth.
你们不能
You don't.
萨姆 一栋建筑
Sam! A building,
行了吧 一栋建筑 在
okayA building in Jefferson City.
密苏里州 在哪 在哪 我要地址
Missouri Where, where An address.
我不知道
l don't know.
我们在找的那个恶魔 它在哪里
And the demon. Where is it.
我不知道 我发誓
I don't know. I swear.
那是全部了 我就知道这么多
That's everything. That's all I know.
结果它
Finish it.
什么 我说的全是真的
What I told you the truth!
我不管
l don't care.
你这个混蛋 你保证过的
You son of a bitch, you promised.
我撒谎
l lied!
萨姆
Sam.
Sam!
继续读
Read.
我们也许还能利用她来找那个恶魔
Maybe we can still use her. Find out where the demon is.
她都说不知道了 她说谎
- She doesn't know. She lied!
何况那里还有个无辜的女孩子
Sam, there's an innocent girl trapped in there and we've gotta help her.
但你这么做会杀了她
You're gonna kill her.
你说什么
What.
你说过 她曾从大楼上坠落
You said she fell from a building.
那个女孩的身体已经损坏了
That girl's body is broken.
她之所以还活着 仅仅是因为那个魔鬼还附在她身上
The only thing keeping her alive is that demon inside.
如果你驱逐了它 那个女孩也就死了
You exorcise it, the girl is gonna die.
但我们也不能让她永远那样活着
We are not gonna leave her like that.
她是个人
She is a human being.
我们要把她从痛苦中解脱出来
We're gonna put her out of her misery.
萨姆 结果它吧
Sam, finish it.
结果它
Finish it.
她还活着
She's still alive.
打911 找些水和毯子来
Call 911. Get some water and blankets.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
慢慢来 好吗
Just take it easy, all right.
来吧 我们让她躺下来
Come on, let's- Let's get her down.
对不起 对不起
Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
行了 行了
I gotcha. Gotcha.
没事了 没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
一年了
A year.
什么
What.
已经一年了
It's been a year.
慢慢说
Just take it easy.
有时我醒着 能感觉到
I've been awake for some of it.
但我不能控制自己的身体
I couldn't move my own body.
我做的那些事 简直是恶梦
And things looked It telling.
关于爸爸的事
the truth about our dad.
迪恩
Dean.
这点我们需要知道
We need to know.
是真的
Yes.
但它要… 你知道
But it wants you to know.
它们就等着你们去救他
They want you to come for him.
只要爸爸还活着 这些都不重要
If Dad's still alive, none of that matters.
我们在找的那个恶魔在哪里
Where is the demon we're looking for.
不在那
Not there.
是另外一个
Other ones.
更可怕的
Awful ones.
它们把他关在哪里
Where are they keeping our dad.
在河… 河边
By the riv- River.
Sunrise
Sunrise.
「Sunrise」 什么意思
Sunrise What does that mean.
那是什么意思
What does that mean.
在医护人员赶来前 你们最好赶快离开这
You better hurry up and beat it before the paramedics get here.
你要怎么跟他们说
What are you gonna tell them.
你不是认为只有你们才知道怎么对警察说谎吧
You think you guys invented lying to the cops.
我会想好故事的
I'll figure something out.
这个 你们拿着 可能用得着
Here, take this.You might need it.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢… 为所有的事情
Thanks for everything.
保重 好吗
- Be careful, all right.
去找到你们父亲
You just go find your dad.
找到他后 别忘了把他带过来
And when you do, you bring him around, would you.
这次我不会想打死他了
I won't even try to shoot him this time.
你一直没说什么话
You've been quiet.
只是在做准备
Just getting ready.
他会没事的 迪恩
He's gonna be fine, Dean.
伙计 你在我的车上画什么东西
Dude, what are you drawing on my car.
那叫做恶魔陷阱
It's called a devil's trap.
魔怪们无法通过或进入
Demons can't get through it or inside it.
有什么用
So.
基本说来 这可以把我们的车变成一个保险箱
Basically turns the trunk into a lockbox.
有什么用
So.
那我们去救爸爸的时候就有地方藏柯尔特了
So we have a place to hide the Colt while we go get Dad.
你在说什么 我们要带上柯尔特
Ninto a lockbox.We're bringing the Colt with us.
我们不能 迪恩
Can't, Dean.
我们只剩三发子弹了
We only got three bullets left.
我们不能随便用柯尔特来对付其他恶魔
We can't just use them on any demon.
我们必须用它来对付那个恶魔
We gotta use them on the demon.
不 我们要救出爸爸 萨姆 知道吗
No, we have to save Dad, Sam.
我们需要所有可能用得上的工具
Okay, we need all the help we can get.
如果我们用完所有子弹 你知道爸爸会有多生气吗
Do you know how pissed Dad would be if we used all the bullets.
迪恩 他不会希望我们带上枪的
- He wouldn't want us to bring the gun. l.
我不在乎 萨姆
don't care Sam.
我不管爸爸怎么想 行吗
I don't care what Dad wants.
而且你从什么时候开始关心他的想法了
Since when do you care what Dad wants.
我们要杀了那个恶魔 你以前也是这么想的
We wanna kill this demon. You used to want that too.
老天 是你来学校找我的
Hell, you're the one who came and got me at school.
是你又把我拖进了这档子事
You're the one who dragged me back into this.
我现在只是在尽力结束这一切
I'm just trying to finish it.
好吧 你和爸爸比我想象中有更多的共同点
You and Dad are more alike than I thought, you know that.
你们俩都迫不及待地想要在这一件事上牺牲自己
You both can't wait to sacrifice yourself.
但你知不知道 我将会是埋葬你们的人
But you know what I'm gonna be the one to bury you.
你很自私 知道吗
It's selfish, you know that.
除了报仇 你不在乎其他任何事
You don't care about anything but revenge.
不是那样的 迪恩
That's not true, Dean.
我希望救出爸爸
I want Dad back.
但它们就等着我们带上枪去
They are expecting us to bring this gun.
如果它们得到了枪 我们就都死定了
They get the gun, they will kill us all.
柯尔特是我们唯一的筹码 这你是知道的 迪恩
That Colt is our only leverage and you know it, Dean.
我们不能带上它 不能
We cannot bring that gun. We can't.
好吧
Fine.
- 我说真的 迪恩 - 我说「好吧」 萨姆
- l'm serious, Dean. - I said fine, Sam.
嗨 嗨
Hey, hey.
我想我知道梅格所说的「Sunrise」什么意思了
I think I know what Meg meant by "sunrise."
混蛋 它们真够狡猾的
Son of a bitch. It's pretty smart.
如果这些魔鬼能附身人类
If these demons can possess people.
它们可能附身于任何人
they can possess anybody inside.
然后让他们袭击我们
Yeah, and make anybody attack us.
在这个充满人肉盾牌的地方 我们没法杀死它们
Yeah, so we can't kill them. A building full of human shields.
它们八成知道我们长什么样
They probably know what we look like too.
这招真毒
Yeah, tell me about it.
是啊 那么 我们怎么进去
All right, so how the hell are we gonna get in.
拉响火警 让不相干的人都撤离
Pull the fire alarm. Get out all the civilians.
但这样消防队会来 大约7分钟是吧
Okay, but then the city responds in what, seven minutes.
没错 7分钟
Seven minutes exactly.
嗨 怎么了 着火了吗
Hey, What's happening Is it a fire.
我们正在检查 先生 靠后站
We're figuring that out now, sir. Just stay back.
我养了只约克狗在楼上 一紧张它就会尿尿
Well, I got a Yorkie upstairs.He pees when he's nervous.
先生 你必须靠后站
Sir, you have to stay back.
我曾经梦想长大后当消防员的
l always wanted to be a fireman when I grew up.
这点你从没和我说过
You never told me that.
我们是消防员 需要你们撤离这里
This is the fire department. We need you to evacuate.
快点
Come on.
爸爸
Dad.
他还有呼吸
He's still breathing.
爸爸 醒醒
Dad, wake up.
爸爸
Dad!
- 等等 等一下 - 怎么了
- Wait. Wait. - What.
他说不定也被附身了
He could be possessed, for all we know.
什么 你是不是疯了
Are you nuts.
迪恩 这点必须确定
Dean. We gotta be sure.
萨姆
Sam.
你为什么往我身上洒水
Why are you splashing water on me.
爸爸 你没事吧
Dad, you okay.
它们迷昏了我
They've been drugging me.
柯尔特在哪
Where's the Colt.
不要担心 爸爸 我们藏在安全的地方了
Don't worry, Dad.It's safe.
好孩子 好孩子
Good boys. Good boys.
嗨 伙计 你不能进去
Hey, buddy. You can't go in.
走
Go.
退后 从后面走
Back, back.
走
Go.
萨姆 我们快走
Sam, let's go.
萨姆
Sam.
萨姆 萨姆
Sam. Sam.
起来 来吧
Come on.Come on.
来吧 我们必须离开这里
Come on. We gotta get out of here.
他怎么样
How is he.
他只是需要休息一下
He just needed a little rest, that's all.
你怎么样
How are you.
死不了
I'll survive.
嗨 我们应该没被跟踪吧
Hey, you don't think we were followed here, do you.
我不知道 我想应该没有
I don't know. I don't think so.
我找不到 比这里更偏远的地方来躲藏了
I can't find more here than in remote places to hide.
是啊
Yeah.
嗨
Hey.
迪恩 你
Dean, you.
你在那里救了我
You saved my life back there.
那我猜你该为我带了枪感到高兴了
So I guess you're glad I brought the gun, huh.
我是在说谢谢你呢
Man, l'm trying to thank you here.
不用谢
You're welcome.
嗨 萨姆
Hey, Sam.
什么
Yeah.
知道我射杀的那个人吗
You know that guy I shot.
那是一个人啊
There was a person in there.
你当时没有选择 迪恩
You didn't have a choice, Dean.
我知道 真正困扰我的不是这个
Yeah, I know. That's not what bothers me.
那是什么
Then what does.
杀死那个人 杀死梅格
Killing that guy, killing Meg…
我一点没有犹豫 甚至没有一点退缩
l didn't hesitate. I didn't even flinch.
为了你和爸爸 我愿意做任何事 杀任何东西
I mean, for you or Dad, the things I'm willing to do or kill.
这个事实…
it's just…
有时让我自己都感到恐惧
It scares me sometimes.
你不该这样想的
It shouldn't.
你做得很好
You did good.
你不生气
You're not mad.
关于什么
For what.
我用了颗子弹
Using a bullet.
生气 我为你骄傲
Mad I'm proud of you.
萨姆和我 对这事都过于执着
Sam and l, we can get pretty obsessed.
只有你- 你一直守护着这个家
But you- You You watch out for this family.
一直都是
You always have.
谢谢
Thanks.
它找上门来了 那个恶魔
lt found us. It's here. The demon.
萨姆 每扇窗每扇门前都撒上盐
Sam, lines of salt. In front of every window, every door.
已经做了
l already did it.
- 那检查一下 行吗 - 好
- Well, check it. Okay - Okay.
- 迪恩 枪在你那 - 是
- Dean, you got the gun Yeah.
把它给我
Give it to me.
萨姆在拯救郡的时候试图射它 但它消失了
Sam tried to shoot the demon and it vanished.
这是我的 我不会射偏的
This is me. I won't miss.
现在把枪给我 快点
Now, the gun. Hurry.
儿子 快点
Son, please.
把枪给我 你在犹豫什么 迪恩
Give me the gun. What are you doing.
你应该火冒三丈的
He'd be furious.
什么
What.
因为我浪费了一颗子弹
That I wasted a bullet.
他不会为我骄傲的 他会把我大骂一顿
He wouldn't be proud of me. He'd tear me a new one.
你不是我爸爸
You're not my dad.
迪恩 是我
Dean, it's me.
我比任何人都了解我爸爸
l know my dad better than anyone.
你不是他 你中什么邪了
- You aingt him. What's gotten into you.
这个问题该问你 退后
I could ask you the same thing. Stay back.
迪恩 发生什么事了
Dean. What the hell's going on.
你哥哥他疯了
Your brother's lost his mind.
他不是爸爸
He's not Dad.
什么
What.
我认为他被附身了
I think he's possessed.
自从我们发现他时 他就被附身了
He's been possessed since we rescued him.
别听他的 萨姆
Don't listen.Sam.
迪恩 你怎知道
Dean, how do you know?
他变了
He's- He's different.
我们没有时间讨论这个
You know, We don't have time for this.
萨姆 如果你想杀死那个恶魔
Sam, you wanna kill this demon.
你就必须相信我
you gotta trust me.
萨姆？
Sam.
不
No.
好吧
Fine.
既然你们都那么确定 开枪啊
You're both so sure.Go ahead.
杀了我
Kill me.
我就知道
I thought so.
这件事竟然变得这么难缠
What a pain in the assthis thing's been.
是你 是吧？
It's you, isn't it?
我们已经找你很长时间了
We've been looking for you a long time.
干得不错 你们找到我了
Well, you found me.
但圣水的事怎么解释？
But the holy water…
你觉得那种东西有可能伤到我吗？
You think something like thatworks on something like me?
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you.
哦 那真是个不错的恐吓
Oh, that would be a neat trick.
事实上 枪就在这里
In fact, here.
让它飞到你跟前呀 小子
Make the gun float to you there, psychic boy.
这真有趣
this is fun.
今天我不止一次能够杀死你 但…
I could've killed youa hundred times today, but this.
这还是值得等待的
This is worth the wait.
你爸爸 他正和我在一起
Your dad, he's in here with me.
被困在他自己的这副皮囊里
Trapped inside his own meat suit.
顺便说一句 他向你们问好
He says hi, by the way.
他要撕碎你
He's gonna tear you apart.
- 他要尝尝你血的味道 - 离开他
- He's gonna taste the iron in your blood. - Let him go.
- 否则我向上帝发誓 - 干什么？
- Or I swear to God- What?
你和上帝能做什么？
What are you and God gonna do?
看看吧 对我来说 这才叫正义
You see, as far as I'm concerned, this is justice.
还记得那个被你们驱逐的吗？
You know that little exorcismof yours?
那是我女儿
That was my daughter.
- 谁 梅格 - 巷子里的那个？？
- Who, Meg? - The one in the alley…
那是我儿子
that was my boy.
你明白吗？
You understand?
- 你在开什么玩笑 - 怎么了？
- You gotta be kidding me. - What?
只有你才能有家庭？
You're the only onethat can have a family?
你毁了我的孩子
You destroyed my children.
如果我杀了你的家人 你会怎样？
How would you feel ifI killed your family?
哦 对了
Oh, that's right.
我忘了 我已经做了
I forgot, I did.
不过 一尸不能抵两命
Still, two wrongs don't make a right.
你这个混蛋
You son of a bitch.
我要知道原因 你为什么这么做？
l wanna know why.Why did you do it?
- 你是说为什么杀了妈咪和漂亮的小杰西 - 没错？
You mean, why did I kill Mommy and pretty little Jess? - Yeah.
我从没告诉过你
You know, I never told you this.
但萨姆将会向她求婚
but Sam was gonna ask her to marry him.
然后就会整日陪她购物买戒指什么的
Been shopping for ringsand everything.
你想知道原因吗？
You wanna know why?
因为她们太碍事
They got in the way.
碍着什么了
ln the way of what?
我为你制定的计划萨姆
My plans for you, Sammy.
你… 以及所有和你一样的孩子
You and all of the children like you.
听着 你能不能快点说完？
Listen, you mind justgetting this over with, huh?
- 因为我实在无法忍受你的独角戏了 - 真有趣
- I really can't stand the monologuing. - Funny.
那就是你的作风是不是？
But that's all part ofyour m.o., isn't it?
掩饰所有痛苦 掩饰所有事实
Masks all that nasty pain.Masks the truth.
哦 是吗？是什么呢？
Oh, yeah? What's that?
你明白的 你努力 你一直在为这个家庭而努力
You know, you fight and you fightfor this family, but the truth is…
但事实是 他们根本不需要你
they don't need you.
不像你需要他们那样需要你
Not like you need them.
萨姆 他显然才是约翰的最爱
Sam, he's clearly John's favorite.
即使他们争吵不休
Even when they fight.
他对萨姆的关心在任何时候都比对你的要多
it's more concernthan he's ever shown you.
我猜你肯定也为你的子女骄傲 啊？
I'll bet you're real proudof your kids too, huh?
哦 等一下 我忘了 我废了它们
Oh, wait, I forgot.I wasted them.
迪恩
Dean.
不
No!
爸爸 爸爸
Dad.Dad.
爸爸
Dad.
爸爸 不要让他杀了我
Dad. Don't you let it kill me.
迪恩
Dean!
爸爸 不要啊
Dad, please.
迪恩
Dean!
不 停下
No! Don't! Stop.
停下
Stop it.
你杀了我 就杀了爸爸
You kill me, you kill Daddy.
我知道
I know.
迪恩 迪恩 嘿
Dean. Dean. Hey.
哦 上帝 你流了很多血
Oh, God. You lost a lot of blood.
爸爸呢？
Where's Dad?
他在这 他在这 迪恩
He's right here, Dean.
- 去看看他 - 迪恩
- Go check on him. - Dean.
去看看他
Go check on him.
爸爸？
Dad.
爸爸
萨姆 它还活着
Sammy! It's still alive.
还在我身体里 我能感觉到
It's inside me. I can feel it.
你射我
Just shoot me.
快射我 瞄准我的心脏 儿子
You shoot me. You shoot me in the heart, son.
开枪 马上
Do it now!
萨姆 不要 不要 快点
Sam, don't you do it. Don't you do it.You gotta hurry.
我不能坚持太久 开枪吧 儿子 快开枪
I can't hold onto it much longer.Just shoot me, son. Shoot me!I.
萨姆 我求你了 此时此地 我们能结束一切
Son, l'm begging you.We can end this, here and now.
萨姆
Sammy!
- 萨姆 不要 - 你必须做
- Sam, no. - You do this!
萨姆
Sammy!
萨姆 萨姆
Sam.Sam.
听着 坚持住 行吗 只要10分钟就到医院了
Look, just hold on, all right?The hospital's only 10 minutes away.
我很惊讶 萨姆 你为什么不杀死它？
I'm surprised at you, Sammy.Why didn't you kill it?
我以为对此我们早就达成共识了
I thought we saw eye to eye on this.
杀死这个恶魔第一重要
Killing this demon comes first.
比我或者任何事都重要
Before me, before everything.
不 父亲 那不是最重要的
No, sir.Not before everything.
听着 我们还有柯尔特
Look, we still got the Colt.
我们还有一发子弹
We still have the one bullet left.
我们只需重头再来一次 是吧
We should start over, all right?
我们已经找到这个恶魔
l mean, we already found the demon once.